[{"answer": "Well, I was diagnosed with cancer in 2006, and I used cannabis as a last resort to heal myself and was able to stabilize myself.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "In a nutshell, what is this all about?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "All of you, you've all got children?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "You have a 2-year-old I think, right?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "I completely disagree with that.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "The obvious question say well you can't take cannabis and take care of your 2-year-old child on your own, can you?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "I like to eat like maybe half of a cookie, one whole cookie is a little too much for me, depends on the strength.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "What is your dosage?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Do you feel a physical and mental benefit from taking cannabis?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Because I was real sick, and they put me on these -- a lot of medications and I started consuming cannabis and they had to do surgery.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Why do you feel that?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "So, it reduced -- it reduced the pain?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "And it also reduced anxiety, you believe?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "And you all found that?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "And this comes to the central knob of this whole debate for me anyway, which is -- is cannabis, marijuana, is it any different in terms of the potential harm to a parent, to a mother, to a wife, to anybody than alcohol?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "No, it's less harmful.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Do you think it's less harmful, more harmful, the same?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Well, I want to address one thing a moment ago.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "Knowing that, would you be happy for your kids to take cannabis from teenage years?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "You call it coming out of the closet then?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Secret marijuana use?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "You have to be careful, just like any prescription drugs, we keep it very safe, locked away from our daughter.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "But what are the downsides that you have to be careful of?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, I was one of the first women to come out of the closet from the corporate sector and not only that but I had a magazine, that I built $6.5 million company.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "By the way, why are you known as that?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "This is the green rush.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "And you must be thinking -- no disrespect you must be thinking if this carries on being legalized all over America, this is the biggest ka-ching your business is ever going to see, isn't it?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "I say that you need to educate your children.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "What do you say?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "ACHADO: Yes, I do.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Could you make edible cannabis, right?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "I make cookies.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "So, what do you make?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Anything and everything you can do.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Any variety?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "I mean, how has it worked?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "I mean, I think the preconceived view for me when I went to this place is that it was going to be, you know, a little sleazy.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "What was the preconceived view and what did you come out with?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Yes, it's pretty -- it's pretty simple.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Were you surprised how easy it was to get a medical marijuana license?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "I mean, when you look at a state like California where -- and the dispensary that I was in is the largest dispensary in the United States.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "And in terms of the overall debate, has your view about the marijuana debate changed at all?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "And also, you know, I would assume as I've just interviewed one of these pot moms with a thriving business, it will create a whole new world of jobs anyways, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "The reality of that war is very, very dangerous communities and is a nightmare for law enforcement.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "What is the reality of that war?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, it's not undeniable true.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "So, David Evans, I mean, you know, that's all undeniably true and you wish to continue to criminalize marijuana, why?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Piers, you're very poorly informed on the dangers of marijuana.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "If it's no more harmful, why not legalize it?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Yes, I smoked pot in college, of course.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "You're painting a very apocalyptic picture here, Mr. Evans, have you taken marijuana yourself?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Piers, I think most of your listeners know that the information that Mr. Evans is giving us right now is false.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Neill, your reaction to all this?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "The very dark, gloomy picture he was painting?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I really can't find that.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "And from everything that you have gleamed in the making of the documentary over the last year, as you say, a very intensive study you've done on this, is there any logical scientific backed reason why if tobacco and alcohol are legalized, marijuana should not be legalized?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "This country is already seriously medicated.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "What are we doing?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Let me go to Sanjay.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "I mean, what do I tell my 12-year-old who says to me, hey, dad, I thought marijuana was bad for you and they are talking about legalizing it?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Look, I mean, he's taking a very safe path here.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "Sanjay, what is your reaction to how Samuel says there?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "See, to that to me sounds absolutely ridiculous.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "Do you think it should be a schedule one substance?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "No, I wouldn't make them legal.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "So you would decriminalize all drugs?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "So you would fine people but you wouldn't imprison them.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "There would have to be some kind of misdemeanor, because what am I going to do -- tell my children is marijuana and heroin is as safe as an aspirin?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "It's extraordinary, Piers, if you think about it.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Sanjay, I don't know if you touched at all, Sanjay, your documentary, but in terms of the way America is now trying to legislate this, what do you think is the most sensible course of action?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "The most definitive data has revolved around two areas.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Is there scientific research that supports the theory, if you're under 25, it could have more effect on you emotionally, psychologically that when you're over 25?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "I mean, aren't we being irresponsible to our children to set them up to have another thing out there to get more dysfunctional and have more problems emotionally?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I think we do a responsibility.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Don't we have a responsibility?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "Well, that we're going about it all wrong.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "What are the key conclusions that you personally have drawn about the marijuana debate?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I haven't really heard any that make sense.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "What is the argument you've heard against what you think that has made the most sense to you?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "RENIER: Yes, I think we've sort of carried of this tradition of this war on drugs where all drug dealers are bag and drug dealers are evil and we should treat them as such by throwing them into jail.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "You think all the arguments are kind of based on traditional views of I just don't like drugs, full stop?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I think we need to educate the youth of America.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "How do you tackle the easing of legislation perhaps with marijuana with the harder stuff?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I personally can't see any reason why that shouldn't be on the table.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Is there a coherent argument that all drugs should be legalized and controlled?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Only on set.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "This morning?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Is it going to happen?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "RENIER: Look, if it doesn't, I will pack my bags and move and you'll never see me again.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "Is that a definite?", "qSentId": 621}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "I should be confident?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Two or three.", "docId": "130816pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "How many could you use?", "qSentId": 650}]